Haven't I made everything work out all right!?
（ナツキ･スバル）
俺のおかげで どうにか
なってきただろ！
Without me, it would've been a lot worse!
俺がいなけりゃ もっと
ひどいことになってた！
All of it was because I was there!
みんな 俺が
俺がいたおかげだ！
You should have a greater debt to me
than you could ever repay!
お前は 俺に―
返しきれないだけの
借りがあるはずだ！
ハア ハア ハア…
Shall we stop for now?
（ヴィルヘルム･
ヴァン･アストレア）
そろそろ終わりにいたしますかな？
So I'll repay all of them now.
（エミリア）
だから それを全部返して―
And end this once and for all.
終わりにしましょう
I swear, Julius, your good
nature is going to waste,
（フェリックス･アーガイル）
ユリウスってば ほんと損な性格
going out of your way to play
the villain for someone like him.
わざわざ 悪役買って出ちゃって
I haven't the slightest idea
what you're talking about.
（ユリウス･ユークリウス）
さて 何のことか
私には分かりかねるが
Why would you go and get yourself
punished trying to protect a guy like that?
（フェリックス）
あんな子 守ろうとして
謹慎処分なんて バカみたい
It's foolish!
I only acted as I pleased,
true to my own nature.
私は己に従ったまでだ
ただ正しく 己らしく
恥じずにあろうと 望むままに
Righteously, in my own way,
and without shame, as I wished.
（フェリックス）いいんですか？
Are you sure about this?
Old Man Wil is busy preparing too.
ヴィル爺(じい)だって
あの剣の準備で忙しいのに
It was a request from our guest.
（クルシュ･カルステン）
客人たっての依頼だ
むげにはできまい
I cannot ignore it.
If they're just practicing,
it's nyo big deal, but...
稽古にゃらいいんですけどね
Frankly, it appears to me
he's just making excuses.
正直 フェリちゃんには―
言い訳をしてるようにしか
見えません
Excuses?
言い訳？
He wants to say, "I'm just fine. I'm working hard."
俺は大丈夫だ
俺は頑張ってるんだっていう
Can you blame him?
無理もないだろ
Forgive me.
（ラインハルト･
ヴァン･アストレア）
すまなかった
Whoa, hang on!
待てって
What do you have to apologize for?
何をどうして
お前が謝る必要があるんだよ
None of this was your fault!
お前が悪いことなんて
何もありゃしねえだろ
No, I am a friend to you,
as well as to Julius.
（ラインハルト）いや
（スバル）え？
僕は君ともユリウスとも友人だ
My own lack of virtue was
responsible for my failure
友人どうしの行き違いを
止められなかったのは―
to stop a disagreement
between my two friends.
僕自身の不徳のなすところだ
That duel had no meaning.
あの決闘には
何の意味もなかった
No meaning?
何の… 意味もない？
Indeed.
What came of you two fighting there?
あの場で２人がぶつかって
何があった？
You were hurt,
君は傷つき ユリウスも
自身の経歴に泥を塗っただけだ
and Julius tarnished his own career.
Why not try to have a calm,
open discussion with him?
一度 冷静に腹を割って
話し合ってみないか？
そうすれば
すぐに誤解もなくなって…
I'm sure that will clear up the misunder—
Reinhard.
ラインハルト
I get how you feel, and I appreciate it.
お前の気持ちは分かったし
うれしいよ
You really are a nice guy.
お前はホントにいい奴だ
Then...
なら…
But I can't accept that proposal!
でも その申し出は受けない
話は終わりだ　帰ってくれ
We're done talking.
Go back now.
Subaru...
スバル… どうしてだ
Why?
What did you gain from that duel?
君は あの決闘で何を得た
失ったものばかりじゃないのか
You've only suffered losses.
Even Emilia-sama—
エミリア様のことだって…
You'd better head back for today, Reinhard.
（スバル）
今日は帰れよ ラインハルト
Before your mistress gets lonely
and starts yelling for you.
お前のご主人様が
さみしくて わめき出さないうちに
Mind your own damn business.
余計なお世話だってんだよ
Shall we stop for now?
そろそろ
終わりにいたしますかな？
Good work on today's practice, Subaru-kun.
（レム）
稽古 お疲れ様でした
スバルくん
（スバル）
レムはさ 俺のこと
情けないとか思わないのか
Hey, Rem...
Don't you think I'm pathetic?
I do.
思いますよ
What, seriously?
（スバル）思うのかよ
Then why are you still here
with a pathetic loser like me?
なら何で 情けない俺と
一緒に残ってんだ
Because you were told to?
そう言われたからか？
The fact that I think you're pathetic
情けないと思うことと
一緒にいることとは―
and my staying with you are not contradictory.
矛盾したりしませんよ
Besides, even if I had not been ordered to,
それに 命じられていなくても
レムはきっと残ってました
I'm certain I would have stayed.
Why?
（スバル）何でだ
Because I want to.
レムがそうしたいからです
明日 出かけませんか？ スバルくん
Shall we go out tomorrow, Subaru-kun?
You haven't gone anywhere
in the three days since we arrived.
ここに来てから３日間
どこにもいってないでしょ
（カドモン･リッシュ）
お前も王選に興味あんのか？
Royal selection got your interest too?
Whoa!
おお！ いきなり
その顔で近づくなよ
Don't sneak up on me
with that face of yours!
Wait, where's Rem?
て… レムは？
（スバル）
ああ… 素人を店に立たすな
Don't make someone without
experience watch your shop.
Five candidates, huh?
候補者は５人か
If you ask me, letting a half-elf
be one of them is pure insanity.
まあ ハーフエルフが
入ってるってのは―
イカれてるとしか思えねえが
"Emilia," eh?
エミリアねえ
There's no way a relative
of the witch could become our ruler.
魔女の係累が
王様になれるわけねえだろうが
They've gotta be crazy.
バカも休み休み言えってんだよ
Why does everyone say that?
（スバル）みんながみんな―
It doesn't mean she has anything
to do with the witch!
その魔女だか何だかと
関係があるってわけじゃねえだろ
Huh?
あ… ハーフエルフだからって
ひとくくりにして―
Just because she's a half-elf,
don't lump them together and brush her off!
勝手に見切りつけんなよ！
H-Hey...
おい！
That Emilia girl... I mean...
その エミリアって子だって―
She might really care about
this kingdom's people, too!
すげえ こう… 国のためにとか
思ってるかもしれねえじゃねえか！
Hang on, why are you getting so worked up?
待てよ 何を必死になってんだ
I...
俺は…
It was for you, wasn't it?
自分の… ためでしょ
Why does everyone...
何でだ 嫉妬の魔女が理由か！
Because of the Witch of Envy?
You think all half-elves are dangerous,
その魔女様ってのが
ハーフエルフだったから―
just because the witch was one!?
ほかのハーフエルフも
全部危ないってのかよ！
That's right!
そうだよ
Everyone's scared of the witch.
魔女が怖い
That's just the way it is.
それは当たり前で
誰もが持ってる共通認識だ
It's common sense.
As long as people see her that way,
そう思われてる以上
はなから 勝ち目なんかねえのさ
she's doomed to failure.
…ったく 誰が好き好んで
担ぎ上げたのやら
Jeez,
what kinda idiot would actually support her?
Try not to say the word
"witch" too loudly in public.
あんまり おおっぴらに往来で
魔女って単語を出すのはやめておけ
You never know who's listening, or where.
どこで誰が聞いてるか
分かったもんじゃねえ
You didn't tell me
（スバル）
みんながそう思ってる
なんてこと―
everyone felt that way about you...
教えてくれなかったじゃねえか
I can't understand if you don't tell me, Subaru.
（エミリア）
言ってくれなきゃ
分からないよ スバル
I can't understand if you don't tell me, either.
俺だって 言われなきゃ
分かんねえよ
Natsuki Subaru, would you
mind joining me for a bit?
（クルシュ）
ナツキ･スバル
少しつきあわないか
Crusch-san... Right?
（スバル）
クルシュさん… か
That's right.
そうだが？
Oh, yes...
そうか 執務を離れた格好を
卿(けい)に見せるは 初めてだったな
This is the first time you've
seen me out of business attire.
The breeze is pleasantly cool tonight.
今日は夜風が涼やかでいい
Perfect conditions for sharing a drink
夜空を見ながら酒をたしなむのに
絶好の日和だ
as we gaze upon the night sky.
But I can't drink alcohol.
俺 酒は飲めねえんだけど
You're welcome to drink water.
水をなめるだけでもいい
I won't be drinking enough to get drunk.
私も酔うほど
飲むつもりはないからな
どうだ？ ゲートの治療のほうは
How goes the healing of your gate?
H-Hey!
（フェリックス）にゃにゃーん
（スバル）ちょ ちょっ…
Oh...
ああ… 一応… 順調に
Well, it goes, I guess...
I see.
（クルシュ）
うん まあ フェリスは
優秀な治癒術師だ
Well, Ferris is excellent with healing magic.
You can trust him.
任せておくといい
You seem like you've always got
something going on too, Crusch-san.
クルシュさんも
ずっと忙しそうにしてるよな
In response to a certain occurrence,
当家では 今―
ある出来事に際して
人と物を集めている最中でな
my family is currently
gathering people and objects.
Plus, since word of the royal selection spread,
おまけに 王選の話が広まって以降
縁談の話が連日きている
I've received proposals every day.
I'm sure the other candidates have as well.
ほかの候補者も同じだろうな
P-Proposals!?
縁談って つまり
結婚ってことだよな？
You mean, as in marriage?
Oh, yeah.
そっか みんな独身だもんな
I guess they are all single.
Does that bother you?
気になるか？
別に　ただ…
Not really.
It's just...
Oh, right!
ああ そう ヴィルヘルムさん
Wilhelm-san said he had a beautiful wife.
きれいな奥さんがいるって
前に言ってたなあ… と
Are you aware that Wilhelm serves me?
ヴィルヘルムが
私に仕えている経緯を―
卿は聞き及んでいるのか？
Huh? Why?
は？ 何で…
What are nyou doing here, Subaru-kyun?
にゃんでスバルきゅんたら
ここにいるわけ？
And Crusch-sama!
それにクルシュ様
そんな無防備な格好で！
Why are you dressed so vulnerably!?
Is it strange?
おかしいか？
It's no different than what
I wear to dine with you.
普段 フェリスと晩酌する時と
変わらないだろう
That's exactly the problem!
そーれーがー
ダメって言ってるんです
Men are nyothing but wolves!
男はオオカミにゃんです
You're a man too, you know.
お前も男だろうが
That's enough joking, Ferris.
戯れはよせ フェリス
All who were present at the royal selection
ナツキ･スバルの思い人が
誰であるのか―
know whom Natsuki Subaru loves.
王選の場にいた
全員に知れている
Yeah. It seems they had a fight, though.
まあ ケンカしちゃった
みたいですけどね
I swear, Subaru-kyun, you're an open book.
もう ホントにスバルきゅんてば
分っかりやすいんだから
Don't cast your gaze down, Natsuki Subaru.
（クルシュ）
下を向くなよ ナツキ･スバル
Huh?
瞳が曇れば魂が陰る
When your eyes are clouded, your soul darkens.
That means your future is closed to you,
それは 未来を閉ざし
生きる意味を見失うということだ
and you lose sight of your reasons to live.
When you do what you know to be right,
己の正しきに従う時―
what can you do by looking downward?
下を向いて行う者に
どれほどのことができる
Lift your head, face forward,
顔を上げ 前を向き 手を伸ばせ
and reach out your hands.
I do not want to regard you
as an insignificant enemy.
私は卿のことを つまらぬ敵とは
思いたくないのでな
（フェリックス）
クルシュ様が
そうおっしゃるにゃら―
If Crusch-sama says so,
you have nyo choice.
しかたにゃいですね
The point is, Subaru-kyun, you need to hurry
and make up with Emilia-sama.
とにかく スバルきゅんは―
早くエミリア様と
仲直りしてくれなきゃ
Think about what you can do to accomplish that,
そのために 何ができるのか
やれるのか―
and do it.
それを費やして尽くすの
（スバル）
俺に 何ができるのか…
What I can do?
There is something I can do.
（スバル）
できることなら ある
Something that only I can do.
俺にしかできないことならある
Yeah, that's right.
ああ そうだった
You don't even have to tell me.
言われるまでもねえさ
The wind is picking up.
風が出てきたな
It looks as if the weather will
be rough again tomorrow.
明日はまた 少し荒れた
天気になりそうだ
Shall we stop for now?
そろそろ
終わりにいたしますかな？
Don't be silly.
ご冗談を
You've seen how much better
I've gotten at taking blows!
俺の受身の上達ぶりを
みましたかよ
Your attitude seems quite different this morning.
今朝はこれまでと
気構えが違うご様子ですが
昨日の夜 クルシュさんに
お悩み相談してもらったんですよ
Last night, Crusch-san gave me some good advice.
If I just get a chance,
I can make any problem disappear!
（スバル）
きっかけさえあれば 何もかも
問題なんて消えてなくなる
（ヴィルヘルム）ふむ
Then, let us call it a day.
では 本日は
ここまでということにしましょう
Huh?
Well, I believe that learning swordsmanship is meant to strengthen a man.
いえ
強くなる選択肢を捨てた相手に
強くなるための剣を説くことは―
To teach it to one who has decided to forsake strength would defeat the purpose.
あまり意味のないことではと
思ったものですから
What do you...
そりゃ どういう…
Subaru-kun!
（レム）スバルくん
（スバル）ん？
We must discuss something important.
大事なお話が
Has Rem told you what's going on?
話はレムから聞いているか
What I felt was...
（レム）
レムが感じたのは―
something like a presence,
through the sense I share with my sister.
姉様との共感覚を通じた
気配のようなもので―
My sister could have used her
clairvoyance to get a clearer picture, but I...
姉様の千里眼なら もっと詳しい
状況も拾えたはずですけど
So I guess you picked up a nyasty
sort of synesthesia from her, huh?
その感じだと―
不穏な感じの共感覚が
きちゃったのかにゃ？
We don't know the details, either.
（クルシュ）
詳細は こちらでも分からない
But it came from the Mathers domain,
だがメイザース領 つまり
ロズワール辺境伯の領地だな
which you know as Margrave Roswaal's territory.
Evidently, some troubling movement
was seen in the vicinity of his mansion.
彼の屋敷のある辺りで
やっかいな動きがみられたらしい
Parts of the domain are already on high alert.
すでに 領内の一部は
厳戒態勢とのことだ
Troubling movement?
やっかいな動き？
もともと 予想された事態でもある
We did foresee this situation.
From the moment the margrave declared
his intention to back Emilia, a half-elf.
辺境伯がエミリアを―
つまり ハーフエルフを
支援すると表明した時点でな
You mean there's trouble happening
because of that prejudice?
そんな偏見で いざこざが
起きてるってのか？
That is likely a correct summation.
（クルシュ）
大筋は それで正しいだろう
The moment I leave her side, this happens?
（スバル）
俺が離れたとたんに これかよ
Everyone around her is an enemy.
周りは敵だらけじゃねえか
The only one who can take her side...
味方になってやれるのは―
is me.
俺しかいねえだろ
Well, then...
だったら―
We have to go and help, right?
助けに行かなきゃいけないよな
Y-You mustn't, Subaru-kun.
（レム）
いっ いけません スバルくん
You have to obey Emilia-sama's orders.
エミリア様の言いつけを
守らなくては
She told you to focus on healing!
スバルくんは
治療に専念するようにと
And I agree!
レムも同意見です
今は体の治療が最優先で…
Healing must take priority now.
Rem,
レム 俺たちしかいないんだ
we're the only ones who can take Emilia's side!
エミリアの味方になってやれるのは
You heard that, Crusch-san.
聞いてのとおりだ クルシュさん
We're going back to the mansion,
back to where Emilia is.
俺たちは 屋敷に
エミリアの所に戻る
Until it's taken care of, my healing will—
事が片づくまで 治療はお預け…
Natsuki Subaru.
（クルシュ）ナツキ･スバル
If you leave here,
ここを出るのであれば―
that will make you my enemy.
卿は 私にとって
敵ということになる
Allow me to correct one idea you have.
１つ 卿の考えを正しておこう
I have only allowed you to stay here
as a guest, receiving treatment,
卿を客人として扱い
治療を受けさせているのは―
because I am contracted to do so.
ひとえに契約があるからだ
Contracted?
（スバル）契約？
Emilia and I formed a contract
regarding your treatment.
卿の治療に関して―
私とエミリアの間には
ある契約が結ばれている
However,
だが―
if you abandon that contract yourself,
そちらから契約を手放すのであれば
守り続ける義理はない
I am not obligated to continue protecting you.
The moment you leave this household,
卿が当家を離れた時点で―
Emilia and I will not hesitate
to become enemies.
私とエミリアは 遺恨なく
敵どうしというわけだ
勘違いしてたぜ
I was wrong about you.
I thought, just maybe,
you and I could get along.
あんたとはひょっとしたら―
仲よくできるんじゃ
ないかと思ってた
Yeah, of course... That was just
a little joke over drinks, right?
だよなあ あんなの
酒の席のざれ言だよな
I was stupid to take you seriously
できることをやれ なんて―
when you told me, an enemy,
to do what I could.
敵に言われた言葉
真に受けた 俺がバカだ
You don't want me to leave
because getting Emilia
ようは ピンチのエミリアを
助けられたら困るから―
out of trouble will be bad for you, right?
俺を行かせたくねえんだろ
Nyow I think you have it all wrong—
勘違いしにゃいで
ほしいんだけどさあ…
Ferris, enough.
フェリス よせ
No, I will say it.
いいえ 言います
The mistake he's making is a bit too grave.
ちょこーっと
勘違いがひどすぎますから
Even if you leave, nothing will change.
スバルきゅんが行ったって
状況は変わったりしない
You'd be wasting your time.
行くだけムダ
After making a fool of yourself at the castle
王城で あれだけ
無様(ぶざま)をさらして―
and being obliterated by Julius,
nyou still don't realize that?
ユリウスにとことんやられて
まだ分からにゃいの？
Stay here and get treated. It's about time
you accept just how powerless you really are.
ここで治療するほうが よっぽど
身の程をわきまえてるってことに
I've made up my mind.
（スバル）
決めたぜ　エミリアの所に戻る
I'm going back to Emilia.
Though it wasn't for long,
thanks for taking care of me.
短い間だけど 世話になった
Is it nyot true that a good man
忠告を素直に受け入れるのも
男のかい性じゃにゃいの？
knows how to take advice?
It's your "advice" that gave me
the last push I needed.
（スバル）
お前の忠告のおかげで決断できた
Thanks for that.
ありがとよ
Rem, how long until we reach the mansion?
レム 屋敷までどのくらいだ
About two and a half days, I think.
（レム）
おそらく ２日半ほどです
Over two days?
２日以上？ 来る時は
半日かからなかったぞ
It took less than half a day to get here!
We cannot go that way.
ダメなんです
街道に霧がかかってしまって―
There is a fog over the road,
so we need to take a detour.
迂(う)回する必要があります
Who cares about fog?
霧が何だってんだよ
The fog is created by the White Whale.
（レム）
霧を生むのは白鯨です
Should we encounter it,
万が一 遭遇した場合―
we would not survive.
命がありません
Thank you for lending us a dragon carriage.
竜車を貸していただき
本当にありがとうございます
In my master's stead,
主(あるじ)に代わり―
I offer my gratitude for the favor you have shown us until today.
今日までのご厚意に
感謝を申し上げます
It's nothing. Please take care.
いえ ご健勝で
Are you getting anything from Ram?
（スバル）
ラムから 何か伝わってきてるか？
No, our shared sense is consciously
controlled, to an extent.
いいえ 共感覚は ある程度
意識して制御していますから
This morning,
今朝の場合も
姉様の自制をとおり越して―
I think that what I sensed was something
that exceeded my sister's control.
レムに伝わってしまった
ものだと思います
So Ram didn't even mean
to let us know about it...
（スバル）
つまり ラムは もともと
俺たちに知らせる気はなかった
Is she trying to keep us from getting involved?
関わらせないようにでも
してるってのか
But why?
何でだよ 俺がいないと
ダメだってのに
She needs me by her side...
I can save her.
俺だったら助けられる
Once I do, I'm sure she'll understand.
そうしたら
分かってくれるはずなんだ
She has to.
絶対に
Why are we stopping?
何で止まるんだ　急がねえと
We have to hurry.
I'm sorry, Subaru-kun.
ごめんなさい スバルくん
The land dragon cannot go any farther.
これ以上は 地竜を
潰してしまいますので
I can't sleep.
寝つけねえ
Subaru-kun, are you awake?
（レム）
スバルくん 起きてますか
Yeah.
I cannot sleep,
寝つけないので 少し話したくて
so I hoped we could talk.
Oh, really? You too?
そっか… レムもか
Can't blame you, I guess.
まあ しかたないよな
I bet you're really worried about the mansion
共感覚で知らされた分―
after what you felt through
your shared sense, right?
レムも めちゃくちゃ
屋敷が心配だよな
It'll be fine.
大丈夫だって
We're not the sort of lovable little kids
to get our feelings hurt so easily.
そう簡単にへっこむほど
かわいげのあるメンツじゃねえ
We'll get right back, and I'll fix things.
すぐ戻って 俺がどうにかするさ
Yes, I have put all my faith in you, Subaru-kun.
はい　レムは
スバルくんを信じています
R-Rem-san,
レ… レムさん？
um, why are you holding on to me?
その… 何で 抱きついて
いらっしゃるんでしょうか
Because I want to.
（レム）
そうしたいからです
H-Huh?
あれ この感じって…
I know this feeling...
I am healing your gate,
フェリックス様と同じ
ゲートの治療ですよ スバルくん
just as Felix-sama did, Subaru-kun.
O-Oh, healing!
おっ ああ 治療… 治療ね
そうですよね ハハハ…
You're healing me... Of course you are.
Because you want to, huh?
そうしたい か…
やっぱり 最初は…
怒られちまうかな
She'll probably be angry
with me at first, won't she?
If you take the time to properly face her
時間をかけて ちゃんと向き合って
自分の気持ちを言葉にすれば―
and put how you feel in words,
I'm sure she will understand.
きっと 分かってもらえます
You are a wonderful person, after all.
スバルくんはステキな人ですから
I am?
（スバル）そう… かな
Yeah... I am, right?
そう… だよな
Emilia is hopeless without me.
俺がいなきゃ
エミリアはダメなんだって…
Because I
俺は こんなに―
care about her... so much...
思って… るんだから…
So please,
ですから―
save just a tiny bit of that for me too.
その ほんの片隅に―
レムのことも
Don't go anywhere.
どこにもいかないでくださいね
Okay, Subaru-kun?
スバルくん
Rem, wake up!
（スバル）
レム 起きろ！
すげえ寝過ごした…
We oversle—
Well, now!
（宿屋の主人）
これはこれは おはようござ…
Good morni—
Where's the blue-haired girl
who was here with me!?
俺と一緒に泊まってた
青い髪の子はどうした！
Th-The lady you were with, u-uh—
お… お連れ様でしたら その…
Speak up, will you!?
聞こえねえよ！
I was saying that she left during the night.
ですから 夜のうちに
出て行かれました
Here are your things...
こちらが お客様の荷物で…
What the hell?
（スバル）
何を… 何を考えてんだよ レム
What are you thinking, Rem?
I thought that you would understand me...
お前は俺を分かってくれるって
そう思ってたのに
（レム）スバルくんへ
"Dear Subaru-kun.
When you read this letter,
この手紙を スバルくんが
読んでいる時―
I'm sure you will be very angry with me.
きっと スバルくんはレムのことを
とても怒っていると思います
I shall not ask
スバルくんを置いて
お屋敷へ向かうレムのことを―
for your forgiveness for leaving you
to go to the mansion.
許してくださいとは言いません
There's a guy in there
who might agree to your offer.
But please understand.
けれど 分かってください
Bringing you to the mansion
right now would be very dangerous.
今のスバルくんを お屋敷へ
連れ帰るのは とても危険です
Are you the one called Otto?
オットーっていうのは あんたか
（オットー･スーウェン）ハア…
I'll accept your payment, but I think this
is very reckless, Natsuki-san!
So please wait here for me to return."
（レム）
ですから スバルくんは
ここで レムの帰りを
待っていてください
So you think I'm a useless
good-for-nothing too, Rem?
（スバル）
お前まで 俺を力の足りない
役立たずだって言うのかよ レム
I think I might've been introduced to
someone who could be real trouble.
これは―
ひょっとして すごく面倒な方を
紹介されてしまったのでは
Okay, fine.
ああ 分かったよ
俺が信じられないなら―
If you won't trust me,
then why should I depend on you?
俺もお前に頼ってなんか
やるもんかよ
I'm sorry, but can we please turn back now?
すいません ここで
引き返させてもらえませんか？
Huh? After coming this far?
はあ？ いまさら ここまできて…
My land dragon is frightened.
（オットー）
地竜がおびえています
It instinctively knows that this place
is too dangerous to approach.
近づいてはいけない場所が
本能で分かるんですよ
Where are we now?
今 どの辺りだ
We're already in the Mathers domain,
すでに メイザース領に
入っています
near a village called Arlam.
アーラムっていう
村の近くで…
Got it!
（スバル）分かった
Natsuki-san, you can't go out there!
ナツキさん 行っちゃいけません
一緒に引き返しましょう
Let's turn back!
This is far enough, Otto.
ここまでで十分だ オットー
My money and stuff are all yours.
金は 荷物ごと
全部持って行ってくれ
You can't be serious.
そんなわけには
とにかく考え直して
Please reconsider this!
Natsuki-san!
ナツキさん！
（スバル）
ハア ハア ハア…
What is this?
何だ…
It's too quiet...
静かすぎる… だろ
何なんだよ…
What was that?
Damn it!
クソッ！
ハア ハア ハア…
I'm back...
帰って… きた
エミ… レムは…
レムはどうしたんだ
Rem...
Rem... What happened to Rem?
Right. Rem...
そうだ レム… レムは
Rem is...
Rem... Rem... Rem... Rem...
レム… レム… レム… レム…
"So please wait here for me to return.
（レム）
ですから
スバルくんは
ここで レムの帰りを
待っていてください
When this is all taken care of,
全てがうまく
片づいたあとで―
I shall return for you.
必ず迎えに行きます
Please take care of yourself.
どうか ご自愛ください
And please... I beg you to wait for my return.
レムが帰るまで お願いですから
待っていてください
Please.
お願いします
From your
スバルくんの―
Rem."
レムより
The  Sickness Called Despair